Harutyun Amirkhanyan

Date of birth: 18 Jun 1994 | **Nationality:** Armenian | **Phone number:** (+374) 77166744 (Mobile) | **Email address:**

har.amirkhanyan@gmail.com | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/harut-amirkhanyan/ | Github:

https://github.com/harutamirkhanyan | Telegram: https://telegram.me/harutyun_a | Address: Armenia (Home)

About me:

Front-End Developer with 1+ year of experience . Skilled in creating Websites, implementing new functionalities to add widgets and templates via Vue.js. Team player with an eye for details.

I express my interest to work for a company with a pleasant atmosphere. In my long-lasting working path I am eager to use my skills for a company and other hand enrich my knowledge from the company experience. I am ready to gain a foothold in the direction of Front-End (Vue) development to expand in it to an expert level.

WORK EXPERIENCE

1 MAR 2022 - 1 MAR 2023 Yerevan, Armenia

WEB DEVELOPERS CODETIME

- 1. Development and Implementation of new modules, templates und widgets
- 2. Bug fixes/ Optimization

1 AUG 2015 - 28 FEB 2022

SALES MANAGER INGO ARMENIA INSURANCE CJSC

2015-2017 • Sales Manager

2017-2019 • Head of Arabkir Branch

2020-2022 • Damage Assessment Specialist

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

1 SEP 2012 – 25 MAY 2017 Yerevan, Armenia

ARMENIAN NATIONAL AGRARIAN UNIVERSITY Bachelor in Insurance

Address Yerevan, Armenia

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ARMENIAN**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	A2	A2	A2	A1	A2
RUSSIAN	B1	B1	B1	B1	B1
GERMAN / ON GOING/	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Hard Skils

Vue.js | HTML | PUG | JavsScript/ES6+ | CSS | GitHub | bem methodology | Gulp | Git | SCSS | Pr imeFaces | yup | Bootstrap

Soft Skills

Communication | Agile (Clickup, Jira) | Teamwork | Multitasking, Ability to work in high pressure | Problem Solving | Time Management